http://www.insightdirect.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
From the same team that brought you ServiceCEO, see the future of Field Service Software: WorkWave Service!
Effective Date: September 4, 2018
At WorkWave LLC ("WorkWave"), we value our relationship with you and place the highest importance on respecting and protecting the privacy of our customers. This Privacy Statement describes how WorkWave collects and uses the personal information you provide. It also describes the choices available to you regarding the use of, your access to, and how to update and correct your personal information. The use of information collected through our services shall be limited to the purpose of providing the service for which the Customer has engaged WorkWave.
When we use the words "personal information," we're referring to information that personally identifies you.
Information We Collect
Some WorkWave products and services require you to register your purchase. During the registration process we ask for your name, business address and phone number, e-mail address and company name. If you register online, your software license and version information may be sent to WorkWave automatically. We may collect credit card or bank account information to process your payments. We may also ask you to answer some optional questions about yourself and your business and how you use the product. We may obtain additional information about you, such as address change information, from commercially available sources, in order to keep our records current.
Tracking Technologies
As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data.
We and our partners use cookies or similar technologies to analyze trends, administer the website, track users' movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level.
We use mobile analytics software to allow us to better understand the functionality of our Mobile Software on your phone. This software may record information such as how often you use the application, the events that occur within the application, aggregated usage, performance data, and where the application was downloaded from. We do not link the information we store within the analytics software to any personally identifiable information you submit within the mobile application.
We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our website or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partners may use cookies or similar technologies in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to opt out of interest-based advertising click here (or if located in the European Union click here). Please note you will continue to receive generic ads.
Collection Of Information In Mobile Applications
When using WorkWave mobile applications and services, we may collect personal information from you such as your phone number, mobile device type, carrier, name, email address, and physical address, as well as the mobile number, device info and location data. We use this information in order to set up and manage your account as well as contact you about your services. If you use location-enabled products and services, you may be sending WorkWave location information. This information may or may not reveal your actual location. You may opt-out of location based services at any time by editing the setting at the device level. We use your information to process and personalize your requests. We also use the information for support, to develop new features, and to improve the overall quality of WorkWave's products and services. We may also use the information to show you a history of your activity, to provide you with statistics about you or your use of our product or service, or to provide you with a better user experience. We may also use your information to contact you about special offerings that may interest you. If you sign up for a mobile message service, you will have the opportunity to stop receiving mobile messages by following the instructions in the message.
Your mobile service provider may be required to monitor your messages for inappropriate content, and that provider may pass on that monitoring obligation to WorkWave. To fulfill these requirements, WorkWave may monitor your mobile messages for inappropriate content.
If you sign up for a WorkWave mobile messaging service through which you have the ability to send mobile messages to other individuals or businesses, you are required to follow all applicable laws, including unsolicited communication laws.
If you sign up for a third-party application or service, we may share information about your mobile device in order to provide the service you requested. Your carrier may have access to information we collect. We suggest that you review your carrier's privacy statement and the privacy statements for any third-party applications or services you use.
Collection Of Information on Behalf of our Customers
WorkWave collects information under the direction of its Customers, and has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. If you are a customer of one of our Customers and would no longer like to be contacted by one of our Customers that use our service, please contact the Customer that you interact with directly. We may transfer personal information to companies that help us provide our service. Transfers to subsequent third parties are covered by the service agreements with our Customers.
An individual or entity seeking access, or who or which seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data may do so by making any required changes directly through use of WorkWave's products and services or direct his query to the applicable WorkWave Customer (the data controller, and in the case of any self-hosted product or service, both the data controller and data processor). In the event of any difficulties doing so, please contact the customer support address applicable to the product or service (or if that does not adequately address the matter, please contact generalcounsel@workwave.com). If a Customer requests the removal of data processed by WorkWave, we will respond within a reasonable timeframe.
We will retain personal data we process on behalf of our Customers for as long as needed to provide services to our Customer and thereafter for so long as we have a reasonable business purpose to retain such data, in any case not to exceed applicable statutes of limitation for contractual claims. WorkWave will retain this personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
How We Use Information
To provide Web Based, Web Connected Services, WorkWave web edition software products are Web-enabled. Some of our Web-enabled products and services may synchronize with the information on your computer to help keep the data accurate and provide additional online services. In some cases, you can manage the frequency of these updates. If you no longer want to synchronize data, you can cancel the service through the service administration pages.
Some products and services permit you to grant access and specify permissions for those you authorize to use the service. As a result, we store the personal information of those granted access. This information may include name, email address, username/ password, and security challenge questions and answers.
WorkWave.com may also implement an online marketplace for Web Applications that run on the WorkWave Platform. When the application is developed by a third party, that third party will be identified and the third party's privacy statement will apply. When applications are developed and offered by WorkWave, this privacy statement applies.
Products and services under this privacy statement are not "HIPAA-ready" or "HIPAA-compliant," and will not assist with or ensure compliance with HIPAA, the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act. You are solely responsible for using these products and services to comply with all applicable federal and state privacy laws relating to medical or health information.
We transmit, store, protect and access all cardholder information in compliance with the Payment Card Industry's Data Security Standards.
WorkWave and its subsidiaries may exchange information about your transactions to fulfill your requests. We may also provide you information about products or services we believe you may be interested in unless you have asked us not to contact you. We offer you the opportunity to review privacy practices at our subsidiaries' Web sites.
Some of our marketing emails have a "Refer-a-Friend" feature that provides you with the ability to automatically send information about WorkWave our Products and Services to your Friends.
Your friend's e-mail address will only be used for the one-time distribution of the information and will not be used for any other purpose.
We offer various Internet chat services. We may or may not encrypt our Internet chat sessions and retain a transcript of the session to help us resolve your current and potential future questions.
Information Security
We protect the confidentiality and security of your personal information from loss, misuse, or unauthorized alteration by using industry-recognized security safeguards such as firewalls, VPNs end encryptions, coupled with carefully developed security procedures. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with applicable law and federal standards. Whenever we ask for sensitive information, such as credit card numbers, we encrypt it as it is transmitted to us.
To access your Web-based services, you will be required to set up a WorkWave user ID and password before you can access the system. Your Web-based services are password protected and we recommend that you do not share your password with anyone. Remember to sign out of your Web-based product and services and close your browser window when you have finished your work. This prevents others from accessing your account if you share a computer or use a computer in a public place, such as a library or Internet café.
We train and require our employees to safeguard your information. We also use physical, electronic and procedural safeguards by restricting access to personal information to those employees and agents for business purposes only. Additionally, we use internal and external resources to review the adequacy of our security procedures.
We may retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.
At WorkWave, safeguarding your personal information is a top priority. WorkWave does not solicit sensitive customer information via e-mail. If you receive an e-mail message that appears to come from us that requests such information, please forward it immediately to: generalcounsel@workwave.com
Information Sharing
We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement.
Sometimes we ask outside firms, or third parties, to help us provide services such as when providing customer service and processing your payments. Our contracts with these third parties outline the appropriate use and handling of your information and prohibit them from using any of your personal information for purposes unrelated to the product or service they're providing.
These third parties are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide the services to us. We require vendors to maintain the confidentiality of the information we provide to them.
We may disclose, access, or report personal information when we believe, in good faith, we're required to by law or to protect our legal rights. We may also do this in connection with an investigation into a suspected violation involving the Terms of Service, fraud, intellectual property infringement, or other activity that may be illegal or expose us to legal liability. For example, we may be required to disclose personal information to cooperate with regulators or law enforcement authorities or to comply with a court order, subpoena, search warrant, law enforcement request, or similar legal process.
We work with other companies or developers to provide you with products and services, which we clearly identify. Either WorkWave or the other company may offer these products and services. We clearly identify these co-branded products and services. In some cases, we exchange customer usage information to establish and provide ongoing service. By requesting these products or services, you are permitting us to provide your personal and usage information to the other company. If you do not want your information shared with these co-branded products, you can deactivate your account by going to your profile or contacting us on the information below.
We also may share information about our users with third parties, such as advertisers or partners, for marketing and promotional purposes. Our Web sites may provide links to third-party sites, such as those of our business partners and online advertisers. These could include other services, promotions or sweepstakes offered by business partners. Because WorkWave does not control the information policies or practices of these third parties, you should review their privacy policies to learn more about how they collect and use personal information.
With respect to residents of the European Union, due to the multinational character of WorkWave, some of the affiliated companies and other recipients listed above may be located in countries (including the United States) that do not provide a level of data protection equivalent to that set forth by the European Union. WorkWave will take appropriate steps to make sure that such recipients act in accordance with applicable law. To the extent that WorkWave transfers user information to recipients which are located outside the European Union, WorkWave will implement appropriate contractual measures to secure such transfer, in compliance with applicable law.
Your Choices
Upon request WorkWave will provide you with information about whether we hold or process on behalf of a third party, any of your personal information. To request this information please contact us by emailing generalcounsel@workwave.com
You may change your account and contact information for WorkWave any time by logging into your account or by emailing generalcounsel@workwave.com. We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe.
To change your mobile contact preferences, follow the instructions in your SMS or other mobile message.
You may unsubscribe from our newsletters by using the unsubscribe link provided in the newsletter sent to you.
Changes to this Privacy Statement
We may update this Privacy Statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this website prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.
How to Contact Us
If you have questions or concerns about WorkWave's collection, use, or disclosure of your personal information, please email us at generalcounsel@workwave.com or write to us at:
WorkWave LLC 101 Crawfords Corner Road Holmdel, New Jersey 07733 Attention: General Counsel
We will endeavor to respond to any questions or concerns within 10 days of receipt.
Copyright 2018 WorkWave LLC. All rights reserved. | Terms of Use | Privacy Policy | End of Life Policy
